Super Spy. Super Fly.
Spies in Disguise is a animation, action, adventure film directed by Nick Bruno.
Super spy Lance Sterling and scientist Walter
Beckett are almost exact opposites.
Lance is smooth, suave and debonair.
Walter is… not.
But what Walter lacks in social skills he makes up for in smarts and invention,
creating the awesome gadgets Lance uses on his epic missions.
But when events take an unexpected turn, Walter and Lance
suddenly have to rely on each other in a whole new way.
Lance Sterling (voice), played by Will Smith.
Walter Beckett (voice), played by Tom Holland.
Killian (voice), played by Ben Mendelsohn.
Marcy Kappel (voice), played by Rashida Jones.
Eyes (voice), played by Karen Gillan.
Ears (voice), played by DJ Khaled.
Spies in Disguise is a 2019 American animated spy comedy film starring Will
Smith and Tom Holland, and produced by Blue Sky Studios.
Directed by Troy Quane and Nick Bruno and written by Brad Copeland and Lloyd
Taylor, the film also stars Rashida Jones, Karen Gillan and DJ Khaled.
The plot involves a secret agent who is transformed into a pigeon by an intelligent young scientist; the two must then
work together to stop a revenge-seeking cybernetic terrorist, and return the agent to his human form.
The film premiered at the El Capitan Theatre on December 4, 2019, and was
theatrically released in the United States on December 25 by 20th Century Fox.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics, and
grossed $172 million against a $100M budget.
It was the final feature film to be produced by Blue
Sky Studios, which closed in 2021.
The film explores themes of inventor, spy, villain, pigeon, aftercreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted.